<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>josh&#39;s tech journey</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on josh&#39;s tech journey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 19:49:07 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Battlesnake Summer League 2021 Reflections</title>
      <link>/posts/battlesnakesummer21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 19:49:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/battlesnakesummer21/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this summer, I learned of a programming competition called Battlesnake. Having acquired a lot of free time after the end of my first year of college, I entered a battlesnake into their summer league competition and took the opportunity to learn Go.
The Competition Battlesnake is a battle royale-esque game where there are initially 4 snakes on the board, each controlled autonomously by a developer&amp;rsquo;s program. In short:
Each snake has a health bar which depletes a little each turn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 23:19:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Formula SAE Data Acquisition I&amp;rsquo;m currently leading the design and manufacturing of a data acquistion system for Sun Devil Motorsports, Arizona State&amp;rsquo;s Formula SAE team. This includes (but is not limited to) the PCB and wiring harness design, sensor selection, embedded software, and data processing scripts. Our code and PCB designs can be found on GitHub while the team website can be found here. The design report for the SDM-23 Data Acquisition system can be found on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:28:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now/</guid>
      <description>What I&amp;rsquo;m doing now This is my now page.
Formula SAE I compete on Sun Devil Motorsports, ASU&amp;rsquo;s Formula SAE team, as the Data Acquisition team lead, where we are responsible for integrating sensors into a Formula-style race car to validate its design and extract the most performance out of it. Currently we are working on a redesign of our data acquisition system to allow for easy modifications, simpler cable runs, and collecting data from the ECU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:28:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me Hi there! My name is Josh, and I&amp;rsquo;m currently studying Computer Science and Mathematics at Arizona State University.
In my free time I enjoy spending time with friends, competing in various competitions, and watching kdramas. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious, here is what I am working on now.
About This Website This website was created in May 2021, is built using Hugo and uses the Cactus theme.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
