<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>josh&#39;s tech journey</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on josh&#39;s tech journey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 19:49:07 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Battlesnake Summer League 2021 Reflections</title>
      <link>/posts/battlesnakesummer21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 19:49:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/battlesnakesummer21/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this summer, I learned of a programming competition called Battlesnake. Having acquired a lot of free time after the end of my first year of college, I entered a battlesnake into their summer league competition and took the opportunity to learn Go.
The Competition Battlesnake is a battle royale-esque game where there are initially 4 snakes on the board, each controlled autonomously by a developer&amp;rsquo;s program. In short:
 Each snake has a health bar which depletes a little each turn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 23:19:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects SC2 AI Arena I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on a StarCraft II bot named Monte. Its page on SC2 AI Arena can be found here and the code can be found on Github.
Battlesnake I competed in Battlesnake&amp;rsquo;s Summer League 2021, and placed in the top four in the gold tier tournament. The code for my bot can be found on Github, and a writeup of its strategy can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:28:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now/</guid>
      <description>What I&amp;rsquo;m doing now This is my now page.
Formula SAE I compete on ASU&amp;rsquo;s Formula SAE team as part of the Data Acquisition subteam, where we are responsible for integrating various sensors into the racecar. This year, I am leading the development of our data dashboard, which will playback recorded data from the car and plot them into various graphs. For the future, we hope to add telemetry viewing to the dashboard where we can view live data from the racecar as it is running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:28:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me Hi there! My name is Josh, and I&amp;rsquo;m currently studying Computer Science and Mathematics at Arizona State University.
In my free time I enjoy spending time with friends, competing in various competitions, and watching animes and kdramas that interest me. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious, here is what I am working on now.
About This Website This website was created in May 2021, is built using Hugo and uses the Cactus theme.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
